<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Creased Paperbacks</title>
    <link>/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Creased Paperbacks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pioneers by David McCullough</title>
      <link>/reviews/pioneers-david-mccullough/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reviews/pioneers-david-mccullough/</guid>
      <description>This book follows the leaders of the Ohio Company of Associates and their settlement into the Ohio territory.
 Manasseh Cutler was to be the spokesman for the “Ohio cause” on the scene with the Congress in New York. The word “lobbyist” had yet to come into use. Rather he was the “agent” assigned to win congressional approval, and no fitter or more capable agent could have been selected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maybe You Should Talk to Someone by Lori Gottlieb</title>
      <link>/reviews/maybe-lori-gottlieb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reviews/maybe-lori-gottlieb/</guid>
      <description>This book describes various therapy sessions as seen through the eyes of a practitioner. Lori’s train-of-thought, running commentary about her conversations with patients provides colour into their lived experiences and makes us empathise with their struggles. She interweaves into the storyline her own experiences and her own conversations with her therapist, creating a rich, autobiographical tapestry which reminds us how emotionally frail each of us can be.
Quotes  We talk to ourselves more than we’ll talk to any other person over the course of our lives but our words aren’t always kind or true or helpful—or even respectful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming by Michelle Obama</title>
      <link>/reviews/becoming-michelle-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reviews/becoming-michelle-obama/</guid>
      <description>The first part of Michelle Obama’s autobiography is particularly worth reading. We all know Michelle as a (former) First Lady, but not so much about her life before that. This first section of the book candidly describes her upbringing in a working class neighbourhood.
 “I’ve been lucky enough now in my life to meet all sorts of extraordinary and accomplished people—world leaders, inventors, musicians, astronauts, athletes, professors, entrepreneurs, artists and writers, pioneering doctors and researchers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>